const fakeData = 
{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Basic Maths",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "normal",
      "question": "1 + 1 is 3",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "normal",
      "question": "Taj Mahal is situated in America",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Sachin Tendulkar scored most tons in cricket",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Technology",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Google's Parent company name is ",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "G.K.",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Aryabhatta invented 0",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Photosynthesis process requires sulphuric acid",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Ussain Bolt is the fastest runner in the world",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Movies",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Learnado Di Caprio won best actor oscar for 'The Revenannt'",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Madam marie Curies invented electron",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
    ]}

export default {
  fakeData
};